sfsuperiorcourt.org 2019-04-20

# Privacy Policy | Superior Court of California - County of San Francisco

#### USER TRACKING AND COLLECTION OF INFORMATION PRACTICES

We collect information such as the following when you visit our website: 

  * Internet protocol address of visitor
  * Time and date of access
  * Internet domain and IP address (from which you are accessing the Internet)
  * Web pages accessed (including search queries: traffic interaction number, case number or party name)
  * Status code (if the transaction was successful, or if an error occurred)
  * Amount of data retrieved

#### HOW WE USE THIS INFORMATION

The data listed above is automatically collected to identify trends in use, measure server performance, to improve the site’s content, and for troubleshooting purposes. This information does not contain personal identities (such as name, address, telephone number, etc.).  

Invisible tags placed on this site’s pages, not on your computer, compile aggregate statistics about usage.  Information collected from you and on this website will not be used for commercial marketing purposes. The Court may disclose this information in response to legal action, such as a court order or subpoena. This information may also be disclosed in response to a request from a law enforcement agency, or where the Court believes it necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or as otherwise required by law.

#### INFORMATION YOU GIVE US

If you send comments or questions regarding this website, we will use your information to respond to you and/or to address issues you identify.  We may also use your comments/questions to improve our services.  

We may also require and record personal information (such as name, address, telephone number, e-mail address) with your active permission, for use of certain website services such as paying traffic citations online.  

#### LINKS TO OTHER SITES

The Court’s website contains links to websites that are not controlled by the San Francisco Superior Court. As these other websites are controlled by third party entities, they are subject to change without warning. When visiting a third party website, you will be subject to the new website’s privacy policy and terms of use.

#### COOKIES 

The Court’s website may utilize cookies to enhance the functionality of the website. Cookies are small text files which are stored on your computer and establish an identifying temporary tag on your computer. These cookies are used for interactive parts of the website, for example, when a search query is done. These cookies do not contain personal information. If desired, they can be disabled on your web browser, but website function may be impacted.

#### DISCLAIMER

Content on this website is intended to provide legal information, not legal advice. The Court is unable to refer you to a lawyer or to provide legal advice.  

Visitors to this website agree that the San Francisco Superior Court is not liable for errors or incompleteness in any information provided on this website. The information may not be re-copied or re-distributed without consent. The Court disclaims any and all liability if information is obtained from a third party entity. 

#### CONTACTING THE WEBSITE

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, kindly contact: [courtwebadmin@sftc.org ](mailto:courtwebadmin@sftc.org)
